{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048578341","data":{"timestamp":" 947048578341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_M-W-P"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048583585","data":{"timestamp":" 947048583585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-N"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048595242","data":{"timestamp":" 947048595242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_K-J-W"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048604131","data":{"timestamp":" 947048604131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_R-M-W"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048610782","data":{"timestamp":" 947048610782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-F-T"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048620006","data":{"timestamp":" 947048620006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_B-J-W"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048641595","data":{"timestamp":" 947048641595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-D-G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048658817","data":{"timestamp":" 947048658817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048679830","data":{"timestamp":" 947048679830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-Y-I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048683637","data":{"timestamp":" 947048683637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-T-CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048689397","data":{"timestamp":" 947048689395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4886a9d6-37f0-4c79-b9c5-6fc1e5f21a27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.70"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-T-CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048730424","data":{"timestamp":" 947048730423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_S_W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048737029","data":{"timestamp":" 947048737029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_N_W"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048743725","data":{"timestamp":" 947048743724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_W"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048750355","data":{"timestamp":" 947048750354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_W_E"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048757025","data":{"timestamp":" 947048757024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_L_I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048764547","data":{"timestamp":" 947048764546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_L_I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048771206","data":{"timestamp":" 947048771206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_S_D"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048777829","data":{"timestamp":" 947048777829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_F_W"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048785316","data":{"timestamp":" 947048785316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_F_W"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048791947","data":{"timestamp":" 947048791947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_S_W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048798594","data":{"timestamp":" 947048798594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_J_W"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048805244","data":{"timestamp":" 947048805243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_G_W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048817290","data":{"timestamp":" 947048817290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_M_G_W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048834717","data":{"timestamp":" 947048834716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_M_G_W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048852744","data":{"timestamp":" 947048852744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 94d89d61-3543-4b9f-b2a6-71f6528dbf08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_M_G_W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048871968","data":{"timestamp":" 947048871968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048875733","data":{"timestamp":" 947048875732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048879803","data":{"timestamp":" 947048879803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048883424","data":{"timestamp":" 947048883423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048887094","data":{"timestamp":" 947048887094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048891064","data":{"timestamp":" 947048891064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048896856","data":{"timestamp":" 947048896856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048902649","data":{"timestamp":" 947048902649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048908033","data":{"timestamp":" 947048908033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048912351","data":{"timestamp":" 947048912350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048918602","data":{"timestamp":" 947048918602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048922580","data":{"timestamp":" 947048922580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048926767","data":{"timestamp":" 947048926766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048932893","data":{"timestamp":" 947048932893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048936803","data":{"timestamp":" 947048936802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048940151","data":{"timestamp":" 947048940151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048943711","data":{"timestamp":" 947048943711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048947128","data":{"timestamp":" 947048947128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048950273","data":{"timestamp":" 947048950273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048953790","data":{"timestamp":" 947048953790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048957368","data":{"timestamp":" 947048957368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048960605","data":{"timestamp":" 947048960605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048964157","data":{"timestamp":" 947048964157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048968024","data":{"timestamp":" 947048968024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048973969","data":{"timestamp":" 947048973969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048979974","data":{"timestamp":" 947048979974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048984030","data":{"timestamp":" 947048984029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048989797","data":{"timestamp":" 947048989796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 12788795-d461-4d3e-8a53-d17405568e7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049016958","data":{"timestamp":" 947049016958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" c86bb4a4-3ab4-4fc3-9e42-778025105de0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049021125","data":{"timestamp":" 947049021125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" c86bb4a4-3ab4-4fc3-9e42-778025105de0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049023197","data":{"timestamp":" 947049023196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" c86bb4a4-3ab4-4fc3-9e42-778025105de0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049044683","data":{"timestamp":" 947049044682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 3538292b-d406-4e81-a27e-f7805b896156"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049089577","data":{"timestamp":" 947049089576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 3538292b-d406-4e81-a27e-f7805b896156"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049089687","data":{"timestamp":" 947049089687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 3538292b-d406-4e81-a27e-f7805b896156"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049103528","data":{"timestamp":" 947049103528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" bf7d886a-df75-4573-9d98-2275c370e71d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049153418","data":{"timestamp":" 947049153417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" bf7d886a-df75-4573-9d98-2275c370e71d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049153560","data":{"timestamp":" 947049153560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" bf7d886a-df75-4573-9d98-2275c370e71d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049160963","data":{"timestamp":" 947049160963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4d23375b-dba1-4e5d-9090-d68dea4db4c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049229999","data":{"timestamp":" 947049229998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4d23375b-dba1-4e5d-9090-d68dea4db4c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049230076","data":{"timestamp":" 947049230076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4d23375b-dba1-4e5d-9090-d68dea4db4c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049274803","data":{"timestamp":" 947049274802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 4d23375b-dba1-4e5d-9090-d68dea4db4c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049284516","data":{"timestamp":" 947049284516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049336613","data":{"timestamp":" 947049336612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049336782","data":{"timestamp":" 947049336781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049345530","data":{"timestamp":" 947049345530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049360766","data":{"timestamp":" 947049360766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049377157","data":{"timestamp":" 947049377157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" d07df2e6-852c-46e4-b499-01d895f5c2a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049403872","data":{"timestamp":" 947049403872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" e518ea75-5e73-4bca-847d-241be3766d96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049404483","data":{"timestamp":" 947049404483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" e518ea75-5e73-4bca-847d-241be3766d96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049427031","data":{"timestamp":" 947049427031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" e518ea75-5e73-4bca-847d-241be3766d96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049448725","data":{"timestamp":" 947049448725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" cdad73a6-f90b-4e55-b5e7-f7f667efb2a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049457703","data":{"timestamp":" 947049457702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" cdad73a6-f90b-4e55-b5e7-f7f667efb2a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049461588","data":{"timestamp":" 947049461588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" cdad73a6-f90b-4e55-b5e7-f7f667efb2a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049463291","data":{"timestamp":" 947049463290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" cdad73a6-f90b-4e55-b5e7-f7f667efb2a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049481633","data":{"timestamp":" 947049481633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_080225"," gameId":" 012c9502-d343-4f46-88a3-b4813abe39f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}